aromahead.com 2019-07-02

# Privacy Policy - Aromatherapy School and Courses - Aromahead Institute

**Privacy Policy**

**Confidentiality:**  
We respect your privacy and require that you respect the privacy of fellow program participants. We never share emails or personal information without your permission.

We respect your confidential and proprietary information ideas and plans and require that you respect the same rights of fellow program participants and of the Aromahead Institute.

Thus, you agree:

  * Not to infringe on Aromahead Institute’s copyright, patent, trademark or other intellectual property rights.

  * That any confidential information shared by program participants or any representative of the Aromahead Institute is confidential and proprietary.

  * Not to disclose such information to any other person or use it in any manner other than what is taught.

  * That all materials and information provided to you by Aromahead Institute are its confidential and proprietary intellectual property belonging solely and exclusively to Aromahead LLC, and may only be used by you as authorized by us.

  * The reproduction, distribution and sale of these materials by anyone but Aromahead Institute is strictly prohibited.

While you are free to discuss your personal results from Aromahead Institute’s programs, you must keep the experiences and statements, oral or written, of all other participants in confidence.

**Content:**

Program education and information is intended for a general audience and does not purport to be, nor should it be construed as, medical advice, therapy or counseling.

The information contained in program material is strictly for educational purposes. Therefore, if/when you wish to apply ideas contained in this material, you are taking full responsibility for your actions.

There is no guarantee, express or implied, that you will earn any money using the information in these programs. Examples in these materials are not to be interpreted as a promise or guarantee of earnings. Earning potential is entirely dependent on the efforts and skills of the person applying all or part of the concepts; ideas and strategies contained in our course materials.

**Data Protection**

We only collect your data to provide you with the best and most relevant information regarding aromatherapy and aromatherapy education. You are free to provide or redact your information at will at any time.

We try to send you only information that is relevant to your interests and needs, and we do try to clear uninterested contacts from our lists on a regular basis. We occasionally send out (optional) surveys to get your feedback, and may reach out to you to suggest programs, trainings or special offers that we believe you may be interested in.

You are free to choose the type of information that you receive from us through email correspondence. At any time you can update your email preferences, unsubscribe completely or request to be removed from our email list.

If you sign up for one of our free trainings, your name and email address may be passed along to our webinar software platform so that you will be able to access the training that you’ve signed up for. You will receive reminders for the trainings, replay emails and some special offer emails that relate to the training that you can opt out of at any time.

If, and only if, you request a text reminder then your phone number will be passed along to our text provider to send the information that you’ve requested to your cell phone.

If you purchase an online course from Aromahead Institute we will only use your payment data in a secure fashion and will not share any of your payment details with third parties.

Students of Aromahead have forever access to their online courses, so Aromahead will keep their login details safe and secure unless they choose to delete their account and all information within. All other contacts will remain active in our database as long as you are receiving our email correspondence.

You have the right to request access, rectification, and/or erasure of any of your data from our database. You have the right to withdraw consent at any time. You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

**Cookie Policy**

Information about our use of cookies:

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive.

The cookies we use are "analytical" cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily. You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them below:

**Analytics**

The services contained in this section enable Aromahead to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

**Google Analytics (Google Inc.)**

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.

**Facebook Ads tracking (Facebook, Inc.)**

Facebook Ads tracking is an analytics service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects data from the Facebook advertising network with actions performed on this Website. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.

This type of service allows this Website and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Website by the User.

This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.

In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

**Facebook Remarketing (Facebook, Inc.)**

Facebook Remarketing is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Facebook advertising network. Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out. <https://www.facebook.com/legal/FB_Work_Privacy> <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>

**Facebook Custom Audience (Facebook, Inc.)**

Facebook Custom Audience is a remarketing and behavioral targeting service provided by Facebook, Inc. that connects the activity of this Website with the Facebook advertising network. Personal Data collected: Cookies and email address. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy – Opt Out.

**How to provide or withdraw consent to the installation of Cookies**

In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing Cookies.

Through browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that may have saved the initial consent for the installation of Cookies by this website.

Users can, for example, find information about how to manage Cookies in the most commonly used browsers at the following addresses: [Chrome](https://www.google.com/chrome/privacy/Google), [Mozilla Firefox](https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/privacy/websites/), [Apple Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/privacy-preferences-sfri35610/mac) and [Microsoft Internet Explorer](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/internet-explorer-ie11-preview-privacy-statement).

With regard to Cookies installed by third parties, Users can manage their preferences and withdrawal of their consent by clicking the related opt-out link (if provided), by using the means provided in the third party's privacy policy, or by contacting the third party.

Notwithstanding the above, Aromahead informs that Users may follow the instructions provided on the subsequently linked initiatives by the EDAA (EU), the Network Advertising Initiative (US) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (US), DAAC (Canada), DDAI (Japan) or other similar services. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools.

Aromahead recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.

Since the installation of third-party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Website cannot be technically controlled by Aromahead, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, the User is kindly requested to consult the privacy policy for the respective third-party services listed in this document.

Given the objective complexity surrounding the identification of technologies based on Cookies, Users are encouraged to contact Aromahead should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies by this Website.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Aromahead reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to Aromahead. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User's consent, Aromahead shall collect new consent from the User, where required.

**Legal information**

This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation).

This privacy policy relates solely to this Website, if not stated otherwise within this document.

**Information not contained in this policy**

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from Aromahead at any time by emailing: [team@aromahead.com](mailto:team@aromahead.com).

Aromahead LLC P.O. Box 2734 Jackson Wyoming 83001 United States (727) 469-3134

Last Modified: April 9, 2019
